{"data":[{"question":"Although the dog appeared harmless, it, in fact, was quite dangerous.\n\u00a0","a":"Although","b":"harmless","c":"in fact","d":"quite","answer":"3","explain":"- In fact->In fact, it was...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody whom was at the meeting will say anything to the press.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Nobody","b":"whom","c":"will","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"- Whom-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Thanks  in Laura's support, I was able to finish the project.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Thanks","b":"in","c":"was","d":"finish","answer":"2","explain":"- In-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Not many of the person in Britain speak a single word of my language.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"many","b":"person","c":"single","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"- Person-> people","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I will be sure you didn't lock the front door. Here is the key.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will be","b":"didn't","c":"front","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":"- Will be-> am","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Keeping calmly is the secret of passing your driving test.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Keeping","b":"calmly","c":"passing","d":"driving","answer":"2","explain":"- Calmly-> calm","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The fox was unsuccessful on reaching the grapes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"on","c":"reaching","d":"the","answer":"2","explain":"- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It is believed for that the man escaped in a stolen car.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"It is","b":"for","c":"escaped","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"- For-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I think that you are drawn up some excellent plans. I must congratulate you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"think","b":"are","c":"some","d":"must","answer":"2","explain":"- Are-> have","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The critics were strong impressed by her performance.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"critics","b":"strong","c":"by","d":"performance","answer":"2","explain":"- Strong-> strongly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}